PJ  这个法国吐司太好吃了
P.J, this French Toast is so good.
里面松软  外面酥脆
It's fluffy on the inside, crunchy on the outside.
是的  而且你用叉子按下去还会有黏糊糊的声音
Yeah, and when you push it with a fork, it makes a squishy sound.
黏糊糊  黏糊糊  黏糊糊
Squishy squishy squishy.
哦  你们不能要求我永远那么酷
Oh. I can't be cool all the time.
所以说  鲍伯  你为周三做好准备了吗
So, Bob, you all set for Wednesday?
周三  呃  驼峰日  工作周的中间日  你的
Wednesday. Uh...Hump day, middle of the week day, your...
生日吗
Birthday?
是万圣节
It's Halloween.
哦  太好了  我不用准备什么了
Oh. Well, good. I don't have to do anything.
不  你得准备  这可是宝宝的第一个万圣节
Yes, you do. It's the baby's first Halloween.
- 你应该化装  - 哦  还会有别的万圣节的
- You have to dress up. - Oh, there'll be other halloweens.
还会有别的宝宝的
There'll be other babies.
- P.J.  - 嗯
- P.J.? - Yup.
你觉得你能做一顿真正的法国大餐吗
Do you think you could cook an actual French dinner?
嗯  应该吧  怎么了
Well, I think so. Why?
那个  因为我和斯宾塞的一周年纪念日要到了
Well, because my one-year anniversary with Spencer is coming up,
我想用一顿浪漫晚餐给他个惊喜
and I want to surprise him with a romantic dinner.
而且必须是法国料理因为我们是在法语课上认识的
And it has to be French because we met in French class.
噢  那是个下着雨的星期一
Oh, it was a rainy Monday.
第一学年  第三节课
Freshman year, third period.
我们都上了麦德莫索·费舍尔的课
We were both in Mademoisel Fisher's class...
泰迪姐
Teddy?
你用华丽的词藻描绘出美好的回忆
You're painting a wonderful tapestry of words to conjure up a place in time...
这就是我离开的原因
And that is why I'm leaving.
这次又酷了哦
Cool again.
所以  嗯  你觉得呢
So, uh, what do you think?
没问题  我给你们准备大餐  蛮好玩的
Sure, I'll make you guys dinner.Sounds fun.
我们可以在万圣节晚上到你公寓去吗
Can we do it at your place on Halloween night?
这样的话斯宾塞不会起疑心  我也可以让他乔装打扮下
That way Spencer won't suspect a thing and I can make him dress up.
瞧  泰迪都让斯宾塞化装了
See? Teddy's getting Spencer to dress up.
你不能拿我跟十七岁小伙子比啊
You can't compare me to a 17-year-old.
嗯  那倒是
Well, that's for sure.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： 寂_翼  Juliet
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十五集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E15  Le Halloween
达布尼太太
Mrs. Dabney.
还没到万圣节呢  你带个面具干嘛
It's not Halloween yet. What's with the mask?
又是这个听腻了的笑话  哈
Using that old chestnut again, huh?
嘿  还是挺好笑的嘛
Hey, if it ain't broke.
那么你来做什么
Now what do you want?
事实上我想来谈谈万圣节的事
I actually want to discuss Halloween.
我想今年我们也许可以跳过一年一度恶作剧
I was thinking this year we might skip the annual pranks.
我已经过了恶作剧的年纪了
I'm getting too old for pranks anyway.
虽然我已经买好了鸡蛋和剃须膏
Although I did already buy the eggs and shaving cream.
我可以把它们带走
I could take those off you.
鸡蛋当早饭 剃须膏可以用到
I can use the eggs for breakfast and the shaving cream for...
啊  别别别
Ah, bup bup bup bup bup!
我的腿毛
My legs.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你不知道  “别别别”  的意思吗
Do you not know what "bup bup bup bup" means?
听着  我来这儿是要问你点别的事情
Listen, while I'm here, I need to ask you something else.
你能陪我去周三晚上的女士俱乐部会议吗
Can you ride with me to my ladies' club meeting
这样我就可以用共乘车道了
Wednesday night so I can use the carpool lane?
- 我给你报酬  - 多少
- I'll pay you.  - How much?
过程中需要交谈吗
And do we have to talk to each other?
30块钱  你说呢
30 bucks and what do you think?
周三见
See you Wednesday.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
准备好啦
I am ready.
天儿不错  小伙儿  我是袋鼠艾米
Good day, mate. My name's Kangar-Amy.
这些是我的袋鼠宝宝们  查莉和托比
And these are my little joeys, Charlie and Toby.
袋鼠一家  很可爱
A family of kangaroos. That's cute.
可爱
Cute?
我们花了俩小时穿进这些衣服里  就只有一句可爱
It took us two hours to get into these costumes, and all we get is "cute"?
别担心  伙伴儿
No worries, mate.
（注：澳洲广告词）
咱们再来烤只虾
Throw another shrimp on the barbie.
住嘴  鲍伯
Shut up, Bob.
我们继续  查莉  跟爸爸说我们刚刚练过的那句
Go ahead, Charlie. Tell him what we practiced.
我想当公主
I wanna be a Princess.
每个人都想当公主  所以你是一只袋鼠
Everybody wants to be a Princess. That's why you're a kangaroo.
她该说 “万圣节快乐” 的
What she was supposed to say was "hoppy Halloween"!
你的服装呢
Where's your costume?
- 呃  穿着呢  - 这是你的工作服啊
- Uh... I'm wearing it. - Those are your work clothes.
是的  不  我演的是
Yeah! No, I'm a...
我今年打算扮演害虫终结者
I'm going as an exterminator this year.
害虫终结者
An exterminator?
好吧  我在袋鼠屁股里汗流浃背
Okay, I am sweating my marsupial butt off
你就只扮演一个杀虫的
in here and that's the best you came up with?
好吧  等等  我还没说完  还有一个  你知道吗
All right. Well, hang on. I'm not done. I'm not done. You know what?
哈
Huh?
现在
There.
我是超级英雄害虫终结者
I'm a superhero exterminator.
叫我终结号船长
I'm Captain Extermo.
你的助手是谁  农药皮特
Who's your sidekick? Pesticide Pete?
妈妈  这个糖果好难吃
Mommy, this candy's yucky.
怎么会
What?
米特大叔的蜂蜜球
"Uncle Milt's Honey Globs."
你为什么要买这么恶心的糖
Why did you buy this disgusting candy?
才不恶心呢  而且在打特价
It's not disgusting. It was on sale.
成分  蜂蜜
"Ingredients: Honey...
球
Glob."
鲍伯  去买些好点的糖果
Bob, go get some better candy.
嗯  鲍伯现在不在
Uh...Bob's not here right now.
我是终结号船长
I'm Captain Extermo.
好吧  你看到鲍伯的话  告诉他我有话要说
Okay. Well, when you see Bob could you tell him I'd like to speak with him?
呃  谁要和鲍伯说话
Uh... Who would like to speak to him?
袋鼠艾米还是艾米
Kangar-Amy or Amy?
艾米
Amy.
喔  他好像已经走了好一阵了
Ooh, he may be gone for a while.
周年快乐
Happy anniversary!
惊喜吧
Surprise!
我带你来巴黎啦
I took you to Paris.
你好
Bonjour.
欢迎来到PJ餐厅
Welcome to Chez PeJhay.
你说什么
What?
PJ餐厅
Chez PeJhay.
PJ的餐厅
Chez P.J.
哦
Oh!
蠢呼呼的游客
Stupid tourists.
我装饰的这个餐厅
So I decorated the place and P.J.
PJ要给我们烹饪正宗的法国大餐
Is going to cook us an authentic French meal.
不过  我没说过要带法国口音啊
Although, we didn't discuss the accent.
要做好法国菜  要像个法国人
To cook French, you must be French.
你们的位置
Your table.
嗒嗒
Tadah!
呃  我觉得嗒嗒说是法语不如说是魔术师用语
Um, I think "tadah" is more magician than French.
你的位置
Your table.
（法语：瞧）
瓦拉
Voila!
今晚的菜单
Your menus for the evening.
就一道菜
There's only one thing on it.
非常明智的选择
An excellent choice.
那么现在  音乐
And now, the music.
嘿
Hey!
是埃米特
Emmett's here.
另一件我没说过的事
Another thing we didn't discuss.
每当拉起手风琴  你就永远也拒绝不了演出
When you play the accordion, you never turn down a gig.
呵
Huh.
万圣节晚上一屋子的老太婆
A room full of old ladies on Halloween night.
突然间我又酷不起来了
And suddenly I'm not cool again.
那么  这个工作要多久
So how long is this gonna take?
只要到我拿到奖就好
Just until I get my award.
你要拿奖
You're getting an award?
是的  年度志愿者奖
Yes, for being the volunteer of the year.
是表彰我对于帮助问题儿童的杰出贡献
It's for my work with troubled kids.
但是你讨厌孩子啊
But you hate kids.
但是我喜欢得奖啊
But I do like awards.
而且我提到了我今晚要带
And I may have mentioned that I would bring
其中一个问题儿童来现场
one of the troubled kids with me tonight.
等一下
Wait a minute.
情况有点不妙  不只是老太婆的问题
Something doesn't smell right here, and it's not just the old ladies.
你带我来这儿是为了的一个傻乎乎的奖
You brought me here just so you could get a stupid award!
万圣节快乐  哈哈
Happy Halloween!
你被耍啦而我吃到糖啦
You've been tricked and it's my treat.
你来开门
You take this one.
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat!
嘿嘿  好吧
Hey! All right.
给你
There you go.
嘿  这件衣服真酷
Hey, that is one cool costume.
我想是狼蛛吧
I'm thinking wolf spider?
是的  好多人都看不出来我扮演的是什么
Yeah. I'm really into bugs.
是吗  我的也是
Yeah? Me too.
猜猜看
Check it out.
我是终结号船长
I'm Captain Extermo.
是超级英雄害虫终结者
A superhero exterminator?!
太帅了
Awesome!
我能和你照张合影吗
Can I get a picture with you?
耶  当然
Yeah! Sure.
亲爱的  能过来下吗
Honey, you wanna come over here?
有人要和终结号船长合影哦
Somebody wants a picture with Captain Extermo.
什么
What?
你扮演的是什么  吃了另一只狗的狗
What are you supposed to be? A dog that ate another dog?
我是袋鼠
I'm a kangaroo.
这是我的袋鼠宝宝
And this is my joey.
就帮我们照相就好
Just take the picture.
请允许我奉上第一道菜
May I present the first course?
牛杂碎
Sweetbreads.
嗒嗒
Tadah!
我查字典了  嗒嗒是可以的
I looked it up. "Tadah" is acceptable.
（注：牛杂碎谐音糖果面包）
嗯  面包和糖果  两样都是我最喜欢的
Mm. Bread and sweets.Two of my favorite things.
我认为我嘴里现在绝对不是这两样
Neither one of which is in my mouth right now.
- 服务员  -你好
- Garcon? - Oui?
这道菜里放的到底是什么呢
What exactly are in these sweetbreads?
啊  嗯  你吃的这份是胰脏
Ah! Uh, you have pancreas.
这位先生的是胃壁
nd the gentleman has stomach lining.
祝您好胃口
Bon Appetit.
埃米特
Emmett.
- 想来点牛杂碎吗  -不了  不过我知道谁会喜欢
- Do you want any sweetbreads? - No, but I know who might.
看起来他们好几周没吃过胰脏了
It's like they haven't had pancreas in weeks.
你知道吗  泰迪
You know what, Teddy?
这一切真的太好了
This is really nice.
真的  就好像我真的参加了巴黎游一样
Well, it was as close as I could get to a trip to Paris.
另外  再想想我们初次相遇的地方  更完美了吧
Plus, I thought it would be perfect considering where we first met.
哦  是的  当然
Oh, yeah. Of course.
是的  我永远不会忘记的
Yeah, I'll never forget it.
我们相识在法语课上  我不小心掉了钢笔然后你说
We were in French class and I dropped my pen and then you said...
嘿  钢笔耶
"Hey, a pen."
不  不是的
No no.
你捡起来  亲手交给我然后你说
You picked it up, you handed it me, and you said...
您的笔  小姐
"Votre plume, mademoiselle."
哦  对的  就是这样
Oh, yeah. Of course.
你是不是什么都不记得了
You don't remember any of this, do you?
实话说  是的
Honestly, no.
我们在哪儿见面真的有这么重要吗
But does it really matter where we met?
有这么重要吗
Um, does it matter?
那只不过是我们恋爱萌芽的地方而已
It's only the beginning of our relationship.
斯宾塞  我们以前还说过以后要一起去巴黎的
Spence, we talked about how we both wanted to go to Paris someday.
我真难以置信一直以来都是我在费心经营
I can't believe I went through all this trouble
而你甚至都不记得
and you don't even remember!
-等等  你要去哪儿  -离你越远越好
- Wait, where are you going? - As far away from you as I can get!
我知道你们对牛杂碎有意见了
I understand there's a problem with the sweetbreads.
现在  基于她长期不懈得致力于问题儿童
And now, for her tireless work with troubled kids,
我非常荣幸得宣布  今年“年度最佳志愿者”的得主是
it is my sincere pleasure to present our "volunteer of the year" award
埃斯特尔·达布尼
to Estelle Dabney.
谢谢
Thank you.
除奖章以外  还有500美元的奖金
And along with a plaque, comes a check for $500.
噢  我差点把这部分给忘了
Oh. I had almost forgot about that part.
我相信你一定会把这些钱
I assume you'll be putting that money
用在关于问题儿童的工作上
towards your work with troubled children.
不然我还能用在哪儿呢
What else would I do with it?
去买一套金银线织物运动衣
Buy a gold lame tracksuit?
我被耍得还不够吗  还要让我看到这种画面
It's not enough I got tricked, I gotta see that?
现在
Now...
我们希望听听今天跟你一起来的
I was hoping we could hear from the young man you brought with
小男孩怎么说也许他有一些话要说
you tonight.Maybe he could say a few words?
噢  还是不用了吧
Oh. That's not a good idea.
他非常爱惹麻烦
He's very troubled.
噢  我很乐意来说几句
Oh, I'd be happy to say a few words.
我将要说什么完全取决于500元里我能拿多少
The type of words I say will depend on my cut of the 500.
这是敲诈
That's blackmail.
你猜对了
That's right.
谢谢  老太婆们
Thank you, old ladies.
我叫盖比
My name is Gabe and,
在这儿是想告诉大家一个真实的达布尼女士
I'm here to tell you the real story about Mrs. Dabney.
五五分
Fifty-fifty.
这个女人
This woman...
就是我的天使
Is my angel.
泰迪
Teddy...
很抱歉我忘了我们是怎么邂逅的
I'm sorry I forgot how we met.
这不仅仅是忘了细节的问题
It's about more than forgetting a few details.
有时候我只是觉得
Sometimes I just feel like...
我比你更重视这段感情
I'm more into this relationship than you are.
还记得我们分手的那段时间吗
Remember that period when we were broken up?
记得
Yeah.
知道那有多久吗
How long was that?
不清楚  大概九个月
I don't know. Like nine months?
八个月十九天四小时
Eight months, 19 days and four hours.
哇
Wow.
泰迪  我人生中最美好的事就是遇见了你
Teddy, you're the best thing that's ever happened to me.
我不记得我们邂逅的情景
I may not remember the moment we met,
但是我可以让这一刻被铭记
but can still make this a moment to remember.
我们该怎么做
How are we gonna do that?
好吧  我有一个主意
Well, I have an idea.
额  你们介意先闪吗  我们正要享受这一刻的时光
Uh, do you guys mind? We're just trying to have a moment here.
介意  你们的时光毁了我们的万圣节派对
Yeah, and your moment is ruining my Halloween party.
好的  嗯  为什么你们要穿小丑的戏服
Okay. Um... Why are you guys all dressed up in clown suits?
因为我们是小丑
Because we're clowns.
那么严格地说  你们并没有为万圣节打扮
So technically, you're not dressed up for Halloween,
你们只是穿着工作制服罢了
you're just wearing your work clothes.
我刚才跟你说什么来着
That's kinda what I've been saying.
你到底站在哪边
Whose side are you on?!
鬼知道你们那儿做的是什么饭  让我的鼻子很难受
And whatever you're cooking over there... It's hurting my nose.
是吗  好吧  你的脸还让我的眼睛很难受  笨蛋
Yeah? Well, your face is hurting my eyes, Bozo.
我有名字
I have a name.
好吧  你叫什么
Okay. What is your name?
砰砰
Boom-boom.
我是丁克斯
And I'm Tinkles.
砰砰和丁克斯
Boom-boom and Tinkles,
你们的名字听起来就像是我的小弟弟在尿布上拉的那什么
You sound like two things my baby brother makes in his diaper.
嘿  谁也不准嘲笑我们的名字
Hey! Nobody makes fun of my name!
但是当我们走在街上的时候总是一直被嘲笑
Sure we do. We got that whole bit where we walk down the street...
闭嘴
Shut up!
事情还没完呢  小姑娘
This isn't over yet, missy.
你惹错小丑了
You messed with the wrong clowns.
噢
Oh.
告诉你  让我怕一个绿头发并挂着大微笑的小丑
You know, it's a little hard to be scared of somebody
这真是太难了
with green hair and a permanent smile!
-好了  够了    -说说而已  天呐
- Okay, that's enough. - Just saying, geez.
丁克斯  宾客  波波  是时候穿上你们的大鞋子了
Tinkles, Binky, Bo-Bo, time to put on the big shoes.
咱们有事儿干了
We got some work to do.
我知道也许达布尼夫人有时会生气
I know sometimes Mrs. Dabney looks mean.
但是在那怒容背后
But underneath that scowl...
是皱起的眉头
There's a frown
在那皱起的眉头背后
And underneath that frown...
带着些许痛苦
There's a grimace.
但是如果你一直剖析剖析剖析
And if you keep chipping and chipping and chipping...
在那背后
Underneath that...
你可以找到暴怒
You'll find a snarl.
再仔细看看
Move it along.
接着  只要再一点点的剖析
And then, with just a little more chipping...
在那背后
Underneath that...
其实是笑容
You'll find a smile.
一个
A smile...
可是温暖我心灵的微笑
That has warmed my heart.
从此改变我人生的微笑
And changed my life forever.
谢谢  盖比
Thank you, Gabe.
太令人感动了
That was very moving.
现在让我们好好享用甜点吧
Now let's take a break for dessert.
哇
Well.
这句话是我以前从没说过的
Here's something I've never said before...
干得棒啊
You did good.
谢了
Thank you.
我要说的是  我很佩服你把这些无能的老太婆们骗得团团转啊
And I have to say, I admire you for scamming these helpless old ladies.
我是厉害  是不是
It was good, wasn't it?
告诉你  我们就是最佳拍档
You know, we make a pretty good team.
那可不是吗
We do, don't we?
什么时候我们得再合作一次
We should team up again.
还有其他的什么骗局吗
Got any other scams?
手上的确有一些
I might have a few.
达布尼太太  这将是我们愉快友谊的开端啊
Mrs. Dabney, this may be the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
就看你的了  小子
Here's looking at you, kid.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
噢
Aw.
你太可爱了  小蜜蜂
Aren't you adorable? You're a bee.
一只九点之前需要回家的小蜜蜂
A bee who's got to be home by nine.
让我来看看有什么糖果
Let's see some candy.
哇哦  这只小蜜蜂知道怎么讽刺
Wow, this bee's got a stinger.
米特叔叔的蜂蜜球
"Uncle Milt's Honey Globs"?
好吧  蜜蜂不是应该吃蜂蜜的吗
Well, bees like honey, right?
这就是件衣服罢了  女士
It's a costume, lady.
好的  明年见
Okay, see you next year!
得了吧
Doubt it.
见鬼
What the...!
-嗨  妈咪   -房子里有蝙蝠
- Hi, Mommy. - There's a bat in the house.
-蝙蝠    -刚刚飞进去
- A bat?!  - It just flew in.
快弄出去  弄出去  弄出去
Get it out, get it out, get it out!
噢  等等  等等
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute.
这是除虫队长的工作
This might be a job for Captain Extermo.
你最好求他
You better ask him.
好吧
Fine.
求你帮帮我吧  除虫队长
Please help me, Captain Extermo.
现在说出我的标语
Now say my catchphrase.
除虫队长  下半辈子每晚都给老娘睡沙发
Captain Extermo, sleeping on the couch every night for the rest of his life.
差不多了
Close enough!
今天晚上准备甜品是
And for your cheese course tonight...
美国奶酪
Fromage American.
我觉得还是跳过甜品的那部分吧
I think we'll skip the cheese course.
好主意
Excellent choice.
一般来说上甜品的时间就是给手风琴表演者小费的时候
The cheese course is traditionally when you tip the accordion player.
-滚开   -好的女士
- Go away. - Very good, Madame.
这是最后一次我会被你说服
This is the last time I let you talk me into
来做你法国餐的手风琴手
playing the accordion for one of your fancy French dinners.
这也许是最后一次法国餐
It's probably the last time it'll come up.
现在  额  我觉得好像有人欠我一段时光
Now, um, I believe someone owes me a moment.
那个人是我
I believe I do.
我去开
I'll get it.
噢  嘿  看看  娱乐节目来了
Oh. Hey, look. The entertainment's here.
我没有叫娱乐节目表演啊
I didn't order any entertainment.
好吧  肯定有人叫了因为这儿有一大群小丑
Well, someone did because there's a whole mess of clowns out there.
小丑
Clowns?!
别  别开门
No, don't open the door!
达布尼太太
Mrs. Dabney,
想不到我们狼狈为奸可以配合得这么好
I never imagined our criminal partnership would be so successful.
我们这是天设地造的一对
It's like we belong together.
让我们在一起吧
And we're gonna stay together.
永远在一起
For a long long time.
-你在干什么呢     -我刚刚做了一个最糟糕的梦
- What are you doing here? - I just had the worst dream of my life.
-我们是在跳舞吗  -是的
- Were we dancing? - Yes.
-带着手铐吗  -是的
- In handcuffs?  - Yes!
这说明了什么
What was that about?!
这就是传说中的愧对于心
It's called a guilty conscience!
我们必须归还那钱
We have to give that money back.
噢  你确定
Oh, you think?!
那我们的合作关系还是结束吧
So I guess the partnership is over.
好的  合作过程还是愉快的
Well, it was fun while it lasted.
嗯
Mm.
-抱一个  -小甜心给妈妈抱一下
- Hug?   - Give Mama some sugar.
噢
Aw.
达布尼女士  我们需要把骗来的钱归还了
Mrs. Dabney, we have to give back the money we stole.
“打错了”是什么意思
What do you mean, "who is this?"
嘿  查莉  那个  呃
Hey, Charlie. So, uh...
邓肯家的万圣节够疯狂的
Crazy Halloween for the Duncans.
有只蝙蝠飞进家里来了
There was a bat in the house.
然后又一小段时间  盖比和达布尼太太成为了好朋友
Then for a short period of time, Gabe and Mrs. Dabney were friends.
我和斯宾塞去庆祝我们的一周年纪念日
And then Spencer and I celebrated our one-year anniversary
吃了一个浪漫的晚餐  然后还有
with a romantic dinner and...
被小丑袭击了
A clown attack.
但是其实也没有那么糟糕
But it wasn't actually that bad.
对我而言
For me.
再说一次  我不怕小丑
Then again, I'm not afraid of clowns.
家里有小丑  家里有小丑
Clowns in my house. Clowns in my house.
家里有小丑
Clowns in my house.
好吧  至少他还说得出话来
Well, at least he's talking.
家里有小丑
Clowns in my house!
祝他好运吧  小查莉
Wish him good luck, Charlie.
今晚过得很愉快  以出动一群小丑的代价
We've had a lot of fun here tonight, at the expense of clowns.
但是我想告诉你的是
But we're here to let you know that
小丑是一个特别严肃的职业
clowning is a very serious profession.
需要经过多年的训练
One that takes years of training.
并且今晚你也看到了  我们并不是特别暴力的人
And contrary to what you saw tonight, we are not a violent people.
噢
Ah!
我们只是希望跟其他人一样
We just wanna be treated with the
被爱戴被尊重
same love and respect as everyone else.
好好呆在学校吧  小屁孩
Stay in school, kids.